<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Connor's Investing Research</title><link>https://investing-help.com/</link><description>Recent content on Connor's Investing Research</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Hangry</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 12:47:32 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://investing-help.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is PancakeSwap?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-pancakeswap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 12:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-pancakeswap/</guid><description>What is PancakeSwap? PancakeSwap is a DeFi token that is used to decentralize swapping coins. PancakeSwap is built and is the biggest DEX (Decentralized Exchange) on the Binance Smart Chain. Pancake Swap works by using Binance Smart Chain coins in your cryptocurrency wallet, and swaps that into the chosen token. You can only swap BSC tokens (Binance Smart Chain) into other tokens on the BSC. You can also stake your Pancake Swap tokens for around 120% APY.</description></item><item><title>What is Aave?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-aave/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-aave/</guid><description>What is Aave? Aave is a decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol that allows people to lend out as well as borrow their cryptocurrency. This allows them to avoid the centralized way of doing it, while at the same time saving more. You can either lend out crypto you already own for interest back on it, or you could borrow cryptocurrency while paying a fee. Aave is a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), meaning that it is governed by the Aave token holders.</description></item><item><title>What is Theta?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-theta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-theta/</guid><description>What is Theta? Theta is a decentralized video streaming service that is built to revolutionize the video streaming space. There are two Theta tokens, there is Theta and Theta Fuel. Theta is the governance token, while Theta Fuel is what is used to power the platform.
What Problem Is It Solving? Theta is focusing on fixing a few different problems. Currently, video streaming services such as Youtube, Twitch, Hulu, and Netflix all are centralized, have some sort of fee/ad system to make them money, and poor infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>What is Polkadot?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-polkadot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -1200</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-polkadot/</guid><description>What is Polkadot? Polkadot is a smart contract platform that is built to be interoperable. In the far future, I think similar to the current technology giants, there won&amp;rsquo;t be a single winner. This is why interoperability is so important. Blockchains must be able to work with each other, because without that ability, they will be left in the past. Polkadot already has smart contracts enabled, and is already rolling out it&amp;rsquo;s parachains.</description></item><item><title>What is Chainlink?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-chainlink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-chainlink/</guid><description>What is Chainlink? Chainlink is an oracle token that links the real world to the blockchain. Chainlink is used on smart contract platforms to make smart contracts more expansive in the things that can be coded into them. For example, in a sports betting scenario, the betting odds would change if one team had a large point advantage over another. This is where Chainlink comes in. Chainlink allows these contracts to use information in the outside world.</description></item><item><title>What is Vechain?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-vechain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-vechain/</guid><description>What is Vechain? Vechain is a supply management coin that&amp;rsquo;s used by mostly businesses to revolutionize their company. Vechain is used for many different purposes, from checking if a pair of shoes aren&amp;rsquo;t fake, to the temperature of the truck your steak was transferred in. The use case for Vechain is huge, and they do have proof that this product is functional. Vechain has dozens of partnerships with some big name companies.</description></item><item><title>What is Cardano?</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-cardano/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/what-is-cardano/</guid><description>What is Cardano? Cardano is a smart contract platform that is built for the future. A smart contract platform is used to design decentralized contracts. The way this works is they are if-then contracts. For example, if the weather is above 95 degrees out, then send out a heat advisory warning. This is just one example of the many use cases of these. The biggest smart contract platform currently is Ethereum, with a current market cap of 280 billion, as well around 1.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 Cryptocurrencies to buy for 2021</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/top-5-cryptos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/top-5-cryptos/</guid><description>1) Cardano Cardano takes the cake in my opinion as the safest way to get a high ROI. Cardano is a smart contract token that is being developed by a team led by a co-creator of Ethereum. In August of this year, the Goguen Mainnet will be released. This upgrade will enable smart contracts on the platform. Cardano already has an established ecosystem, even though we are still this far away from this upgrade.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 Stock Trading Platforms 2021</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/top-5-stock-platforms-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/top-5-stock-platforms-/</guid><description>1) Webull Webull takes the cake in my opinion as a stock trading platform. It has 0 fees, after-hours trading, a pretty simple interface, and you can even trade a selection of cryptocurrencies there. They also have a great deal to new investors that includes up to 4 free stocks, that can be valued up to $1850. Overall, a great platform that I have never had a complaint with, and that&amp;rsquo;s why it takes the number 1 spot on this list.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 Crypto Exchanges 2021</title><link>https://investing-help.com/posts/top-5-crypto-platforms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://investing-help.com/posts/top-5-crypto-platforms/</guid><description>1) Binance Depending on where you live, Binance could vary as a top rated exchange. For the people that live in the United States, you have to sign up for Binance US. For people who live outside the US, you can use the normal Binance. The difference between these two is Binance US has a much smaller selection of coins, but the tradeoff with that is it is very secure. The normal Binance is pretty much the opposite, with it having a large selection of coins, but it still quite secure.</description></item></channel></rss>